UNITE Executive Assistant to the President David Melman Papers 6000/048
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
UNITE Executive Assistant to the President David Melman Papers
1989- 1999
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Melman, David
6000/048
1 cubic feet
1 linear ft.
Records.
6992250
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 10, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, February 17, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: 6000 AV: UNITE Audio-Visual Collection 6000 G: UNITE Posters 6000 MB: UNITE Memorabilia 6000 P: UNITE Photographs 6000 PUBS: UNITE Publications
Clothing workers -- Labor unions; Textile workers -- Labor unions; Melman, David; Union of Needletrades, Industrial and Textile Employees; UNITE HERE (Organization); International Ladies' Garment Workers' Union
6992250
- A & Z Industries, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Alle Processing, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Arrow, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Authentic Fitness, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Barneys, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Bayer Clothing Group, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Bidermann, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Bidermann Backup, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Blue Fish Clothing, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Botany 500, 1995-1997 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Brooks Brothers, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Burberrys, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Calvin Klein Cosmetics, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Catitiva, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Chetta B, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- CMA, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- CMA Agreement, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  Scope and Contents
  5/1/95-4/30/98
- Costume Industry, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Cotton Garment, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Cotton Garment Negotiations, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Crown Textile Company, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Crystal Art, 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Cuddlecoat, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Cynthia Steffe, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Dalil Fashions 1995 Bill, 1991-1998 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Dalil Fashions - Miss Scarlett, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Damon Press, 1992-1996 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Danaclon, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Designer Holdings Ltd., 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Designer Holdings Clippings, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Dixie Kids, Fayetteville, NC, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Donegal, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Donna Karan 1/1/92 - 12/31/93 Bill, 1991-1996 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Donna Karan Jeans, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Donna Karan 1996 10-K, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Donna Karan IPO, 1991-1996 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Dorby Frocks, Ltd., 1991-1996 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Ferrara, 1990-1996 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Fieldcrest Cannon, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Fingerhut, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Gap, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Glamour Glove, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Gloria Gay Coats, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Harley Davidson, 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Harley Davidson Apparel, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Hart, Schaffner & Mark, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Harwood, 1989-1996 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Hays Spencer Hays, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Health-Tex, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Kay Co., Inc., 1993-1997 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Hills, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Hollander Gome Fashions, 1995-1999 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- I. Appel Corp., 1996-1998 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- International Branded Apparel, 1990-1996 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Import Restriction (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Jason Tynan, Inc., 1997-1998 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Jay Garment Company, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 57)
- JD American Sportswear, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Jessica McClintock, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 59)
- JH Collectibles, 1995-1996 (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Jonathan Logan, 1993-1996 (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Jones Apparel Group, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Jules Miller & Sons, 1994-1998 (Box 1, Folder 63)